president-elect Donald Trump will be
taking office immediately and then
heading off to vacation this weekend but
he's already got his eye on 20120 in an
interview with the Washington Post Trump
said he's looking forward to trademark
his next campaign slogan which is not
going to be do American cads it's in
2020 he plans to run with keep America
great uh showing just how confident he
is that there will still be an America
in four
years but people online were quick to
point out that they heard that phrase
somewhere before Oh yes keep America
great was tagline for the third andom of
The Purge election
year
but at least he has a consistent vision
for this country so
comedians since that motto might need to
change uh what's another movie inspired
slogan for Trump's 2020 campaign Brian
you want the truth I can't handle the
truth all right very good points very
good Aaron Gibson I'm just a girl
standing in front of a boy asking him to
please not get us in a war with China
all right points
points Judah Freelander uh Toto we're
not in Kansas uh we're in Canada all
right F very
good